<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>English on Xu Zhe&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>http://xuzhe91.com/tags/english/</link>
    <description>Recent content in English on Xu Zhe&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 00:40:23 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://xuzhe91.com/tags/english/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Crawler and Scraper Fundamentals</title>
      <link>http://xuzhe91.com/post/python-spider/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 00:40:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://xuzhe91.com/post/python-spider/</guid>
      <description>Github: https://github.com/xuzhe0628/python-spider-scraper-fundamentals
Content  Web crawler and scraper HTTP Request: GET and POST Capture and parse web via urllib Powerful requests: HTTP for Humans Web scraper framework: scrapy Using API  Prerequisite  Python 3.5 or later version MongoDB (needed if you want to run the Scrapy example)  1. Web crawler and scraper http://stackoverflow.com/questions/3207418/crawler-vs-scraper
A crawler get web pages from a starting page based one some rules or conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math for Data Science</title>
      <link>http://xuzhe91.com/post/math-for-data-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:36:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://xuzhe91.com/post/math-for-data-science/</guid>
      <description>Math for Data Science Review This article is based on Coursera course Math for Data Science provided by Duke University. To better understanding the algorithms in data mining, machine learning and deep learning, I write this summary to go through the basic math that will be used.
Sets A set means a collection of some elements. For example, a basket of vegetables.
** Cardinality ** is the size of a set.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curse of Dimensionality</title>
      <link>http://xuzhe91.com/post/machine-learning-curse-of-dimensionality/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2017 20:30:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://xuzhe91.com/post/machine-learning-curse-of-dimensionality/</guid>
      <description>Curse of Dimensionality As the number of features or dimensions grows, the amount of data we need to generalize accurately grows exponentially.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Causes of Error in Machine Learning</title>
      <link>http://xuzhe91.com/post/machine-learning-errors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2017 20:04:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://xuzhe91.com/post/machine-learning-errors/</guid>
      <description>Bias Bias due to a model being unable to represent the complexity of the underlying data. A high Bias model is said to underfit the data.
Bias occurs when a model has enough data but is not complex enough to capture the underlying relationships. As a result, the model consistently and systematically misrepresents the data, leading to low accuracy in prediction. This is known as underfitting. Simply put, bias occurs when we have an inadequate model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning Performance Evaluation Metrics</title>
      <link>http://xuzhe91.com/post/mlnd-evaluation-metrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 00:00:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://xuzhe91.com/post/mlnd-evaluation-metrics/</guid>
      <description>Type Name Definition Comments     Classification Accuracy number of correctly identified instances / all instances Not ideal for skewed data. Not ideal for situations that you care one classification more than the rest. For example, if you create a model to predict cancer, you may care more about whether the people have cancer other than he does not.   Classification Precision True Positive / (True Positive + False Positive) Out of all the items labeled as positive, how many truly belong to the positive class.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scikit-learn Cheat Sheet</title>
      <link>http://xuzhe91.com/post/scikit-learn-cheatsheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 21:21:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://xuzhe91.com/post/scikit-learn-cheatsheet/</guid>
      <description>Some variables used in the cheat sheet.
clf # the model that we trained X_test # the test dataset y_test # the target of the test dataset  Preprocessing Dataset Split training dataset test_size decides the proportion of instances split from the training set as test data. random_state decides whether the data is randomly chosen.
from sklearn import cross_validation X_train, X_test, y_train, y_test = cross_validation.train_test_split(X, y, test_size=0.4, random_state=0)  Evaluation Metrics Confusion Matrix from sklearn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Central Tendency and Variability of Data</title>
      <link>http://xuzhe91.com/post/statistic-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 21:17:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://xuzhe91.com/post/statistic-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Statistics provide several simple but powerful concepts that we can use to measure the central tendency and variability of datasets. I just want to write my understanding about these concepts.
Measures of Central Tendency Mode
Median
Mean
Variability Quartile
Standard Deviation</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>